Eventually, you will arrive at the stage where
最终 你还需要思考
you want to start thinking about how your strategy will work in practice.
投资策略在实践中的效果如何
This is the portfolio construction stage,
这就是投资组合构建阶段
he stage where you have to think about using
在这个阶段 你需要思考
your combined alpha vector to generate and update an actual portfolio.
如何整合 alpha 向量生成和更新投资组合
At every time iteration,
每次迭代更新
your strategy is going to take an existing portfolio,
你都需要用整合 alpha 向量
make predictions about market behavior using your combined alpha vector and use
对现有的投资组合作出预测
this information to make trades that move the existing portfolio to an updated portfolio.
然后利用这些信息进行交易并更新投资组合
There are more questions that must be answered when turning
将市场假设变成交易时
your market hypothesis into traits such as,
需要考虑更多问题
how does your strategy take into account in various forms of risk?
例如投资策略是如何考虑各种风险的？
What quantities should your portfolio seek to optimize?
投资组合想优化哪些指标？
Are there any additional constraints on your portfolio?
投资组合还有其他约束条件吗？
How do real-world constraints like transaction costs
实际的交易成本等约束条件会减少多少理论收益？
eat into the theoretical return and how can these be mitigated?
如何减少这些约束条件的？
Let's talk in a bit more detail about some of these questions.
我们深入了解下这些问题
You probably already have an intuitive sense of what a risk is.
你可能对风险已经有了直观的概念
It's uncertainty about the future, and in particular,
风险是指对未来的不确定性
the possibility that something bad will happen,
尤其是可能会发生糟糕的状况
like losing the money you invested.
例如损失投资资金
In finance, risk usually refers to uncertainty or
在金融领域 风险通常是指不确定性或收益变化性
variability in returns and there are many different ways to quantify it mathematically.
风险有多种数学衡量方式
There are different types of risks.
风险的种类有很多种
Risks inherent in the entire market are called systematic risks.
整个市场固有的风险称为系统性风险
One form of systematic risk is risk inherent to individual sectors,
各个行业固有的风险就是一种系统性风险
like the technology sector or the energy sector called sector-specific risk.
技术行业或能源行业的风险称为行业特定风险
For example, the success of the energy sector as a
例如 整个能源行业的好坏
whole might be affected by fluctuations in the price of oil,
可能会受到油价波动的影响
but it's unlikely that this would affect the technology sector nearly as much.
但是油价对技术行业的影响就没那么大了
Risk inherent to individual stocks is called idiosyncratic or specific risk.
各个股票固有的风险称为非系统性风险或特殊风险
For example, a single oil company might be uniquely affected by
例如 某家石油公司可能会受到
political events in a region of the world in which it is exploring for oil.
该公司油田所在区域的政治事件的影响
Your strategy will likely incorporate a mathematical model in these risks,
投资策略可能会包含这些风险的数学模型
which will help you understand and manage the different types of risks
从而帮助你了解和管理不同种类的风险
and attempt to avoid being overly exposed to anyone.
并避免遭受这些风险的过多影响
Different investment funds have
不同的投资基金
different mandates driven by the goals of their investors.
会根据投资者的目标采取不同的措施
For example, some funds will want to be neutral to all systematic risk.
例如 某些基金希望对所有系统性风险都保持中立
Whereas, other funds have a specific target for that risk.
而其他基金对系统性风险有特定的目标
Your portfolio could be designed to maximize different objectives.
你构建的投资组合可以最大化不同的目标
As one example, you could seek to maximize expected return and minimize return variance.
例如 你可以最大化预期收益并最小化收益方差
In this case, if two portfolios have the same expected return,
如果两个投资组合具有相同的预期收益
you would choose the one with lower variance.
你会选择收益方差更小的投资组合
Finally, your portfolio may be subject to additional requirements or constraints.
最后 投资组合可能会受到其他要求或约束条件的影响
For example, the policies of your investment firm may dictate
例如 投资公司的政策可能规定
that you can't hold stocks below a certain level of market capitalization,
你不能持有低于某个市值的股票
or you may only be allowed to enter
或者因为某些市场的政府法规
long positions due to government regulations in certain markets,
只能做多股票
or there may be a limit on what percentage of
或者对任何一支股票的投资金额
your portfolio can be invested in any single stock.
存在一定的限制条件
These must be taken into account during portfolio design.
在设计投资组合时必须考虑到这些因素
Finally, in the training stage,
最后 在交易阶段
you make actual trades in the market.
你将在市场中实际进行交易
After portfolio construction, you'll have
构建投资组合后
an ideal portfolio and a list of trades to make.
你将获得理想的投资组合和要进行的交易列表
In this stage, you'll have to figure out mechanics like how
在此阶段 你需要考虑交易速度
fast to trade and to which time horizon you believe your alpha applies.
以及 alpha 适用于哪个时间段
You may decide to trade quickly and aggressively,
你可以主动快速地交易
or more slowly and passively.
或者被动缓慢地交易
You'll also have to take into account the fact that the trades
此外 还需要考虑交易本身也存在成本
themselves incur costs which will eat into your returns.
需要从收益中扣除成本
This is the realm of market microstructure and high-frequency trading.
这属于市场微观结构和高频交易的范畴
Finally, spends market conditions don't allow you to place the exact trades you intend.
最后 某些市场条件不允许你完全按照预期进行交易
As you can see, there's a lot to think about during this process.
可以看出 在此流程中有很多要考虑的事项
So, let's get on with it.
我们开始逐个了解吧